[🎃 Spook-tacular Savings Await! 🕸️ No Tricks, Just Treats: 50% Off Over $100! 👻](https://www.playmobil.com/en-us/web-shop/offers/50-years/)

[🎃 Spook-tacular Savings Await! 🕸️ No Tricks, Just Treats: 50% Off Over $100! 👻](https://www.playmobil.com/en-us/web-shop/offers/50-years/)

Menu

* Play Themes
    
    Back to menu
    
    * Toddler

    * Your World

    * Your Adventure

    * Fans & Collectors

* Interests
    
    Back to menu
    
    * Interests

* New & Exclusive
    
    Back to menu
    
    * Highlights

    * Exclusive

Privacy Policy
==============

PLAYMOBIL® USA, INC.

26 Commerce Drive

Cranbury, NJ 08512

Voice: (609) 395-5566

Fax: (609) 395-3015Customer Service e-mail address: [service@playmobil.us](mailto:service@playmobil.us)

Non-Customer Service e-mail address: [webmaster@playmobil.us](mailto:webmaster@playmobil.us)

PLAYMOBIL® strives to provide a safe and fun online experience. We developed this site to be enjoyable and fun for children and adults.

To enjoy our website, PLAYMOBIL® does not require anyone to share personal information about themselves. You can visit our site without registering with us.

When an adult over age 18 decides to make a purchase from the PLAYMOBIL® Online shop, we will require personal information to complete your purchase and ship your order. We will ask for your name, address, phone number and a valid e-mail address. We will not use the personal information you give us for anything except what we described above. You have the option to opt-in to receiving a newsletter from PLAYMOBIL® and you may review your personal information at anytime by clicking the My Account feature. We do not collect or keep personal information online from children under 13 without a parent's permission.

Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to a visitor's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. PLAYMOBIL® uses a "session" cookie to screen out children under 13 who have unsuccessfully attempted to register at the web site or through the 'Contact Us' button. That cookie will be removed once the browser is closed. Certain limited non-personal identifiable information is recorded by PLAYMOBIL® Internet servers when you visit our site. This limited information includes the type of browser you are using (such as Netscape Navigator or Microsoft Internet Explorer) and the operating system your computer is using (such as Windows 98). PLAYMOBIL® Internet servers also keep track of the number of visitors to the site, the pages they visited and how long they stayed. None of this information includes any personal information about you.

If you decide to set up an account with PLAYMOBIL®, we will ask you to create a login name and a password. You will be the only one who can access your account. When you create an account, you will also have the option to add yourself and your children to the PLAYMOBIL® Wish List. Fans under age 18 can use the Wish List to browse our Online Shop, but they cannot make purchases.

We will keep all information about your purchases even after your order has shipped. You can review your online account at any time without making a purchase. If you have not set up an online account with us, or if you have any questions about our online privacy policies or information we have stored about you, please contact us at [service@playmobil.us](mailto:service@playmobil.us).

PLAYMOBIL is a registered trademark, pronounced playmobeel.

Join our newsletter and get an exclusive 15% off your first order!

 Sign up

* About PLAYMOBIL

* Customer Service

* Catalog

* More

    Select your country / region
    
    Europe

    North America

    USA

©2024 Playmobil. All rights reserved.

* [Cookies](javascript:void(0);)

Hey, please update your browser

Looks like you are using older versions, and you will need a latest one.

Other options are Opera, Safari and Edge
